onedollarinsuranceoffer.com 2018-08-22

# Privacy Policy

_Last updated: July 5, 2018_

Globe Life owns and operates any website that displays this Privacy Policy (each, a “Site”). Your privacy is important to us. We created this Privacy Policy to explain how we collect, use, and share the information that we collect from and about you on this Site. By using this Site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

### Information Collected

_Information You Provide:_ We collect information that you provide to us when you inquire about or purchase products and/or services through this Site. If you refuse to provide any requested information (whether or not required), you may not be able to take full advantage of this Site and its features. Personal information includes any information that can be used to identify or contact you, such as your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number or Social Security number, and any other identifier that permits the physical or online contacting of a specific individual. On certain Sites, we may also collect from you information about your contacts, such as their email address, to share an article or other content.

_Information from Third Parties:_ We may also collect information about you from third parties, like credit reporting agencies or a social media site or a plug-in you use to log into or connect to this Site, and authorize to send us information from that social media account (e.g., name, age, photo). We may associate or combine the information you provide through this Site with this information collected from third parties.

_Information Automatically Collected:_ When you use this Site, the server may automatically recognize you by a “cookie” or other tracking technology. These technologies act as unique identifiers and allow us to tailor this Site to your specified interests and keep track of your activity on this Site. This information may be added to your user profile and used to deliver offers and advertisements that we believe are relevant to your interests.

Furthermore, we may retrieve certain information from your browser (e.g., browser type, referrer URL, date and time of your visit, IP address) and device (e.g., MAC address, device type, screen resolution, and OS version). We use this information to monitor this Site’s performance, analyze traffic patterns and usage, ensure that this Site and any transactions function properly, and gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. This information also may be appended to your user profile so that we may further tailor this Site to your interests and send offers to you based on such information.

Our advertisers, publishers and other third-party partners also may utilize third-party cookies and other tracking technologies like clear pixel GIFs (i.e., web beacons) to identify you. We and our third-party partners may use these technologies to measure responses to e-mails and page views on this Site and our third-party partners’ websites. You can opt out of some of our third-party partners’ use of cookies and other technologies at: <https://www.google.com/settings/ads> (Google), <http://networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp> (various third parties via the Network Advertising Initiative), <http://assets.invitemedia.com/opt-out.html> (Invite Media), and <http://www.clicktale.net/disable.html> (Clicktale).

_Tracking Options and California Do Not Track Disclosures:_ Certain parts of this Site require cookies, and we may use them to deliver more relevant advertising and to link data collected across other devices you use. You can adjust your settings to limit tracking or decline cookies, but as a result you may not be able to use certain features of this Site or take full advantage of all of our offerings. Please refer to your device or browser settings for more information on how to delete or decline cookies and control your tracking preferences. This Site does not respond to do not track signals from most browsers.

### Information Use

We use your information to:   

  * Respond to your inquiries and requests (e.g., emails, fulfillment mailings, newsletters)
  * Complete and fulfill any inquiry for information or purchase you make
  * Help underwrite and provide accurate insurance premium rate quotes;
  * Provide insurers with the required information for applications;
  * Connect you with third-party partners who will provide information about products and services;
  * Market to you and keep you informed of our products and services and/or those of our third-party partners, which we think may be of interest to you
  * Provide, maintain and improve customer service;
  * Tailor your experience with the Services to your interests;
  * Develop new products and enhance and improve our Sites and business;
  * Respond to your inquiries; and communicate with you regarding the insurance products that you purchased through the Site as well as other products and services that may be of interest to you.
  * Allow you to send messages to a friend through this Site
  * In addition, we may aggregate your Information with our other user’s Information and use that information for benchmarking and analysis purposes.

We have a lawful basis for collecting and processing your information if (a) you consented to such processing; (b) we have a legitimate interest for processing your data, like analytics, fraud prevention, improving our Sites and our business, and direct marketing; and (c) we are legally required to process it. 

### Information Sharing

Additionally, we may share your information (a) with other Globe Life And Accident Insurance Company businesses including Globe Life Insurance Company of New York and Globe Life Agency; (b) with third-party partners who will provide you with information about their product and services; (c) with our third-party service providers who provide services like payment processing, IT, and data analysis; (d) with national credit bureaus to verify your identity and obtain your credit report and credit score; (e) if you seek insurance quotes, with financial services providers who offer competitive rates; (f) if you choose to send a message through this Site or contribute to public areas of this Site (e.g., message boards, blogs); and (g)with a third party in the event of a sale or transfer of all or part of our business (including in connection with any bankruptcy proceeding).

We also may access and disclose your information to (a) comply with legal process; (b) to respond to lawful requests from authorities, including public and government authorities outside your country of residence, and including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements; (c) to enforce our terms and this Privacy Policy; (d) to protect our business; (e) to protect our rights, privacy, safety, or property and/or that of others; and (f) as necessary under applicable law, including laws outside your country of residence.

### Other Websites

This Site may contain links to third-party owned and/or operated websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such third-party websites. These third-party websites have separate privacy practices; we have no responsibility or liability relating to such practices; and such practices govern your use of these websites.

We may share your Information with insurance carriers offering the third-party insurance products made available to you through the Services.

We may use third party vendors to assist us with the Service (“Third Party Vendors”). Some examples of the assistance that may be provided by third party service providers are: monitoring and analyzing Site activity, operations and marketing assistance, hosting the Site, and maintaining our database. It is possible that some of these service providers will be located outside of the United States. We may share your Information with these Third Party Vendors but only as necessary for them to perform their functions and to the extent permitted by law. Use of your Information by these Third Party Vendors is governed by their own privacy policies and procedures and not by this Privacy Policy.

We may share your Information with any of our parent companies, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under common control with us.

As we develop our businesses, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, sale of assets, dissolution, or similar event, some or all of the Information may be part of the transferred assets.

To the extent permitted by law, we may also disclose Information when required by law, court order, or other government or law enforcement authority or regulatory agency, or whenever we believe that disclosing such information is necessary or advisable, for example, to protect the rights, property, or safety of us or others.

### Security

We take commercially reasonable steps to protect your Personal Information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. We encrypt sensitive information (such as credit card number) provided. Please understand, however, that no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our databases, nor can we guarantee that the information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to and from us over the Internet. If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure please immediately notify us at 1-800-742-6787.

### Children

We do not knowingly collect, use, or share the personal information of children under age 13 and this Site is not directed to individuals under 13. If we are made aware that we have collected personal information from an individual under age 13 we will delete this information as soon as possible.

### Choices and Access

Residents of certain countries, including European Union member states (and the United Kingdom), may have additional rights listed under “Non-U.S. Residents” below.

_Marketing E-Mails:_ To stop receiving marketing e-mails from us, please click here and follow the instructions to unsubscribe. Even if you unsubscribe, we may still send administrative (i.e., non-marketing) messages. To unsubscribe from a third party’s communications, contact that third party directly or follow the instructions to unsubscribe in the applicable marketing e-mail.

_Certain Sharing with Third Parties:_ To opt out of our sharing of your personal information with third parties for their own marketing purposes, contact us at www.globelifeinsurance.com/contact with your name, address, and phone number and request that we suppress your personal information going-forward. The e-mail address you use to send the e-mail must match the e-mail address in our records. Please note that we will not be able to remove your personal information from the third parties’ databases, and you will need to contact them directly and/or use any available opt-out mechanisms.

_Access and Deletion:_ You may ask whether we hold any of your personal information (or request its deletion) by contacting us at  www.globelifeinsurance.com/contact and providing your name, address, and phone number. The e-mail address you use to send the e-mail must match the e-mail address in our records.

### Retention Period

We will retain your personal information for as long as is needed to provide you with our products and services, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law. Personal information of non-U.S. residents will be stored for six years unless otherwise required for legal purposes or as set forth in “Non-U.S. Residents” below.

### Operation of Our Site and Business

Our Site and business are operated in the United States. If you are located outside of the United States any information you provide to us will be transferred to and processed in the United States. By using this Site or providing us with your personal information, you consent to have your personal information transferred to and processed and stored in the United States in the absence of an adequacy decision or the appropriate safeguards set forth in Articles 45 and 46, respectively, of the General Data Protection Regulation.

### Non-U.S. Residents

For residents of the European Union (and the United Kingdom), Globe Life is the data controller responsible for your personal information collected under this Privacy Policy. In addition, you have the following rights with respect to the personal information collected from and about you on this Site:  

  * The right to request access to such personal information.
  * The right to request the correction, erasure, and/or restriction of processing of such personal information.
  * In some instances, the right to object to the processing of such personal information.
  * In some instances, the right to request that Globe Life export, in a structured, commonly used, and machine readable format, and transmit to another controller, such personal information.
  * The right to withdraw, at any time, any consent to the processing of such personal information.

To exercise these rights, please contact us at www.globelifeinsurance.com/contact

### Your California Privacy Rights

Under California Civil Code Section 1798.83, California residents who have established business relationships with us may choose to opt out of our sharing their Personal Information with third parties for direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and (1) you wish to opt out; or (2) you wish to request certain information regarding our disclosure of your Personal Information to third parties for the direct marketing purposes, please contact us at www.globelifeinsurance.com/contact. Alternatively, you may send a written request to the following address: 

**Globe Life And Accident Insurance, Inc.**  
Privacy Policy  
P. O. Box 268850  
Oklahoma City, OK 73126-8850 

### Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will post an updated version of the Privacy Policy and revise the **“LAST UPDATED”** date at the top. If we change the Privacy Policy in any material way, we will provide appropriate notice to you. Using this Site after any changes are made means you accept those changes and the revised Privacy Policy.

### Globe Life Business

For purposes of this Privacy Policy, “you” or “your” means the person(s) using this Site or the products or services offered through this Site. “Globe Life,” “us,” or “we” includes (but is not limited to) Globe Life And Accident Insurance Company, Globe Life Insurance Company of New York, and Globe Life Agency. Globe Life And Accident Insurance Company is the party responsible for the management of the jointly used information.

### Dispute Resolution

You have the right to submit feedback about this Privacy Policy, or the practices described in it, to the applicable supervisory authority in your jurisdiction of residence. For U.S. residents this is/includes the Federal Trade Commission and/or your state Attorney General. For Non-U.S. residents this is/includes the Data Protection Authority in your country of residence.

### Changes to and Review of Personal Information

If you think that any personal information we have collected from or about you is inaccurate, you may notify us in writing at the address provided below. We will investigate your request and make appropriate changes as needed. 

You may send written request to review or change your personal information to:   
**Globe Life And Accident Insurance, Inc.**  
Privacy Policy  
P. O. Box 268850  
Oklahoma City, OK 73126-8850 

### Contact Us

**Globe Life And Accident Insurance, Inc.**  
Privacy Policy  
P. O. Box 268850  
Oklahoma City, OK 73126-8850
